Ivy Ledbetter Lee Papers, 1881-2003 (bulk 1915-1946): Finding Aid MC085
Public Policy Papers
- Series 9: Visual Materials, 1881-1971; 14 boxes; 1 folder
  - Autographed photographs, dates not examined; 6 boxes
    - Day, Joseph P., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Debevoise, Thomas M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Debose, William F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dewart, William T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dewey, Charles S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dickerman, William C., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dixon, George Dallas, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dowling, Judge Victor S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dunham, Robert T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Dunham, Wallace B., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Egan, Martin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Eisenhart, L. P., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Farrard, Dr. Livingston, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Finley, John H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Fleishhacker, Hubert, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Flexner, Abraham, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Flexner, Dr. Simon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Franklin, P.A., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Gibson, Harvey D., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Grace, Eugene S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Graham, Ernest A., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Gray, Carl R., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Greene, Jerome D., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Grimm, Peter, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Guggenheim, Daniel, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Guggenheim, Harry F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Guggenheim, Simon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Gutierrez, Senator, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Hampden, Walter, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Harriman, W. Averill, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Heinz, Howard, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Hill, George W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Hines, Walter, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Hocking, William, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Hope, W. E., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - House, Colonel E. M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Howard, Roy W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Howell, Clark, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Hutton, Edward F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Inglis, William W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Jackman, Ralph, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Jelke, Frazier F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Kahn, Otto, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Keller, K. T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Kerns, Jerome, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Kingsley, William M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Kelley, Cornelius T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Lamont, Robert P., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Lamont, Thomas W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Lawrence, William T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 145)
    - Lee, Elisha, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Lee, T. G., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Levy, Louis S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Lewis, Charles E., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Lindburgh, Charles, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Loomius, E.E., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Loree, L. F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - MacKay, Clarence, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - MacKenzie, William L., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Marcosson, Isaac F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Mason, Julian, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - McCullock, J.S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - McKinley, Wililiam, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - McRoberts, General Samuel, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Metz, Herman, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Millikan, Dr. R.A., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Mills, E. C., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Morrow, Dwight W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Murname, George, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - O'Brien, John P., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Ochs, Adolph S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Osborn, William Church, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Perkins, George W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Perkins, James H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Pierce, Daniel T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Pound, Dean Roscoe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 146)
    - Powell, Francis E., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Pratt, Herbert L., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Prentice, Bernon S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Robinson, Henry M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Robinson, Richard Hallett?, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Rockefeller, John D. Sr., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Rockefeller, John D. Jr., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Rockefeller, John D. III, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Rowberg, Sigmund, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Salter, Sir Arthur, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Schitt, Mortimer L., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Schwab, Charles M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Scott, Albert L., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Sisson, Francis H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Soong, T. V., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Speyer, James, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Stoehr, Max W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Stone, Melville E., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Strauss, Frederick, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Swope, Herbert Bayard, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Taft, William H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Teagle, Walter C., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Thomton, Sir Henry W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 147)
    - Thirkield, Reverend W. P., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Thomton, Sir Henry W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Traylor, Melvin A., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Turner, Spencer, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Walken, Elisha, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Warburg, Felix M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Ward, James H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Watts, Frank Overton, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Wells, H. G., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - White, F. Edson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Wickersham, George W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Wiggin, Albert H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Wilbur, Dr. Ray Lyman, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Williamson, Frederich Ely?, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Wrench, Sir Evelyn, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Woods, Arthur, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Young, Owen D., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
    - Unidentified Photographs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 148)
  - Films, 1971; 1 box
    - "This Man Speaks for the Great: Ivy Lee Relates an Anecdote for a noted client, John D. Rockefeller, Sr, undated; 1 box (Box 149)
      All versions of "This Man Speaks..." are visual only (no audio). Unknown origin.
    - "This Man Speaks for the Great...," negative, undated; 1 box (Box 149)
    - Ivy Lee, Jr. interview, 1971; 1 box (Box 149)
      Produced by the Foundation for Public Relation Research and Education; Ivy Lee, Jr. interviewed by Allen Center, Vice President of Motorola. 26 minutes in length.
  - Posters, 1918-1943; 4 boxes; 1 folder
    - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1918-1932; 4 boxes; 1 folder
      - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1918-1932; 1 box (Box Box 134)
      - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1918-1932; 1 box (Box 135)
      - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1918-1932; 1 box (Box 136)
      - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1918-1932; 1 box (Box 137)
      - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1918-1932; 2 folders (Folder Oversize folder 1, Folder Oversize folder 2)
    - Pennsyslvania Roailroad "Patriottic posters", Undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 1)
      Includes publicity
    - USSR propaganda posters, 1923; circa 1924; Undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 1)
      Topics include people at the the Lenin Mausoleum on Red Square and airplanes
    - Miscellaneous, 1921-1943; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 3)
      Includes Rockefeller Foundation Information Service foldout, 1921; New York hospital map, 1923; and posters by Boris Artzybasheff, 1942-1943
- Series 10: Exhibit Materials, 1899-1930; 1 box
  This series contains travel-related material, primarily souvenirs and visual material, used in an exhibit on Ivy Lee.
  Arranged by type of material.
  - Europe and Egypt--Menus, 1926-1927; 1 box (Box 150)
  - Europe and Egypt--Miscellaneous, 1899-1928; undated; 1 box (Box 150)
  - European Postcards, circa 1920s; 1 box (Box 150)
  - Japanese Memorabilia Collected by Cornelia Lee, 1929; 1 box (Box 150)
  - Japanese Postcards, 1929; 1 box (Box 150)
  - Russian, German and Other Memorabilia, 1905-1930; undated; 1 box (Box 150)
  - United States Postcards--Seven Pines, Wisconsin, undated; 1 box (Box 150)
  - Medal, undated; 1 box (Box 150)
- Series 11: Microfilm, undated; 8 boxes
  This series contains microfilm of the papers.
  - Positive Service Copies, Reels 1-25, undated; 1 box (Box 151)
    Box 1 – Box 33, Folder 10
  - Positive Service Copies, Reels 26-49, undated; 1 box (Box 152)
    Box 33, Folder 11 – Box 65, Folder 6
  - Positive Service Copies, Reels 50-73, undated; 1 box (Box 153)
    Box 65, Folder 7 – Box 100, Folder 2
  - Positive Service Copies, Reels 74-97, undated; 1 box (Box 154)
    Box 100, Folder 3 – Box 139
  - Silver Halide Duplicate Negatives, Reels 1-48, undated; 1 box (Box 155)
  - Silver Halide Duplicate Negatives, Reels 49-97, undated; 1 box (Box 156)
  - Silver Halide Master Negatives, Reels 1-48, undated; 1 box (Box 157)
  - Silver Halide Duplicate Negatives, Reels 49-97, undated; 1 box (Box 158)